finepix-x100.com 2014-06-18

# Our Privacy Policy | FUJIFILM FinePix X100

FUJIFILM (" **We** " or " **FUJIFILM** ") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

For the purpose of data protection, the data controller is **FUJIFILM UK Ltd** of FUJIFILM UK Ltd, 10a St Martins Way, St Martins Business Centre, Bedford, MK42 0LF, United Kingdom

### How we use information we collect

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To ensure that content from our Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 
  * To help us understand your needs and interests and provide you with better services. Specifically, we use your information to communicate with you, to provide service and support and to update you on relevant services and benefits. Occasionally we may also use your information to contact you for market research regarding our products or services. We will always give you the opportunity to opt-out of market research and customer surveys
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
  * To notify you about changes to our service.

Data collected online may also be combined with information you provide through other sources.

Non-personal data is collected for reporting about our web Site usability, performance, and effectiveness. It is used to improve the customer experience, usability and Site content.

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in a particular area). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.

### Who we share it with

FUJIFILM will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to any other party such as a business partner or a related third party company unless you have given permission to do so.

### Use of cookies

When you visit this Site, you can browse the Site and access information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our Site, we use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, and enables FUJIFILM to record your user journey. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. Cookies help us to improve our Site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. Cookies enable us:

  * To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.
  * To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our Site according to your individual interests.
  * To speed up your searches.
  * To recognise you when you return to our Site. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our Site.

Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.

### Where we store your personal data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (" **EEA** "). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

### External sites

This Site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that FUJIFILM is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Site.

### Disclosures

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 736 of the UK Companies Act 1985.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our employees, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [privacy@fujifilm-digital.com](mailto:privacy@fujifilm-digital.com).

### Access to information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

### Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [privacy@fujifilm-digital.com](mailto:privacy@fujifilm-digital.com).
